Anastasia Gladun

Full Stack Web Developer

PERSONAL DETAILS

Mobile: 021 03 03387

Email: anastasiagladoun@gmail.com
Website: https://anastasia-gladun.netlify.ap

SUMMARY

I have always been passionate about technology and even started my career as an IT manager. However, I wanted to be more involved in the technical part of the process and after a few years of being in and out of the IT world, I decided to chase my passion and become a web developer.

I think that code is a tool for visual creation. I get such joy from building code that transforms your ideas into something real. I really enjoy communicating ideas, collaborating, and sharing knowledge and skills.

I have recently graduated from Enspiral Dev Academy, where I practiced agile methodologies and had experience in dev tools while developing a range of software applications and working in diverse teams. For the final project, my team and I created a complete web app from scratch, both the back end and the front end using HTML5, CSS3, React, Redux and MySQL. I had an opportunity to demonstrate an ability to learn fast and work with strict deadlines and apply my skills while learning new tools and technologies and communicating with the team.

KEY SKILLS

Technical skills

- JavaScript, ECMAScript 6.
- React.js, Redux, JSX.
- Node.js, Express.js, Handlebars.js (server-side rendering and APIs).
- MySQL, Knex.js, PostgreSQL.
- Unit testing: Supertest, Cheerio, Jest.
- HTML5, CSS3, ¡Query, Skeleton, Bootstrap.
- GitHub, Command line.
- Pair-programming.
- Agile practices.

Soft skills

- Customer service experience.
- Problem-solving.
- Multi-tasking.
- Ability to work in a team and individually.
- Planning and organizational skills.
- Self-management, time-management.

EXPERIENCE

Enspiral Dev Academy

March 2021 - August 2021, Wellington

16 weeks of code Bootcamp in an industry-style environment, providing experience using industry tools and creating a foundation for full-stack web development. The course work included HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, React, Redux, SQL, testing, pair programming, agile (scrum) practices, along with human skills, teamwork, and communication.

Web development program projects:

- Personal Blog
- Scale

Wellington Sourdough

June 2019 - April 2021, Wellington Pastry chef

Croc Incorporated

January 2011 - December 2015, Moscow

Moscow System Integrator / Service Delivery Manager

Responsibilities

- Customer service and support in Computer and Storage System Department.
- Coordinating service calls for warranty support/Responsible for meeting SLA requirements.
- Cooperation with leading IT hardware vendors: Dell, HP, IBM, EMC, Oracle, Hitachi, Symantec.
- Coordinating the work process between several departments and work teams.
- Part's logistics management, using vendors' control systems.
- Presentations for new colleagues.

EDUCATION

• Enspiral Dev Academy, 2021 Wellington

Qualification: Web Development Training Scheme

• **Udemy, 2021** *Online*

Qualification: The Complete Web Developer in 2021: Zero to Mastery

The National University of Science and Technology, 2011 Moscow
 Qualification: Applied computer science